Batwo AI Marketing - ads_management Permission Demo
바투 AI 마케팅 - ads_management 권한 데모
This permission allows users to create and manage advertising campaigns.
이 권한으로 광고 캠페인을 생성하고 관리합니다.
Click the "Create New Campaign" button in the Campaigns menu.
캠페인 메뉴에서 "새 캠페인 만들기" 버튼을 클릭합니다.
The campaign creation form is displayed.
캠페인 정보를 입력하는 화면이 표시됩니다.
Campaign name: "Test Campaign for Review"
캠페인 이름: "Test Campaign for Review"
Campaign objective: Conversions
캠페인 목적: 전환 (Conversions)
Budget setting: ₩10,000
예산 설정: ₩10,000
Select the campaign duration dates.
캠페인 기간을 선택합니다.
Enable the "Sync to Meta" option.
"Meta에 동기화" 옵션을 활성화합니다.
This option ensures the campaign is automatically created in Meta Ads Manager.
이 옵션으로 캠페인이 Meta Ads Manager에 자동 생성됩니다.
All information has been filled in.
모든 정보 입력을 완료했습니다.
Click the "Create Campaign" button.
"캠페인 생성" 버튼을 클릭합니다.
API call: POST /act_/campaigns
API 호출: POST /act_/campaigns
The campaign has been successfully created in Meta.
캠페인이 Meta에 성공적으로 생성되었습니다.
A completion message is displayed.
생성 완료 메시지가 표시됩니다.
Return to the campaign list.
캠페인 목록으로 돌아갑니다.
The newly created campaign appears in the list.
새로 생성된 캠페인이 목록에 추가되었습니다.
"Test Campaign for Review" status is "Active".
"Test Campaign for Review" 캠페인의 상태는 "활성"입니다.
Open the campaign menu to demonstrate status change.
캠페인 메뉴를 열어 상태 변경을 시연합니다.
Click the "Pause" button.
"일시중지" 버튼을 클릭합니다.
API call: POST / with status=PAUSED
API 호출: POST / with status=PAUSED
Campaign status has been changed to "Paused".
캠페인 상태가 "일시중지"로 변경되었습니다.
This change is immediately reflected in Meta Ads Manager.
변경사항은 Meta Ads Manager에도 즉시 반영됩니다.
Click the "Resume" button to reactivate.
"재개" 버튼을 클릭하여 다시 활성화합니다.
API call: POST / with status=ACTIVE
API 호출: POST / with status=ACTIVE
Campaign is reactivated.
캠페인이 다시 활성화되었습니다.
With ads_management permission, you can:
ads_management 권한으로 다음을 수행할 수 있습니다:
- Create new advertising campaigns - Edit existing campaigns - Pause and resume campaigns - Delete campaigns
- 새 광고 캠페인 생성 - 기존 캠페인 수정 - 캠페인 일시중지 및 재개 - 캠페인 삭제
When users create campaigns in our app, they are automatically reflected in Meta Ads Manager.
사용자가 우리 앱에서 캠페인을 생성하면 Meta Ads Manager에도 자동으로 반영됩니다.
Users can manage all campaigns exclusively through our app.
사용자는 앱에서만 모든 캠페인을 관리할 수 있습니다.
ads_management permission demo completed.
ads_management 권한 데모를 완료했습니다.